hey what's up everybody thanks for
listening to The Grow Your Life podcast
my name is Jeremiah Kowski and I talk
about how coaches mentors and trainers
can scale their businesses to make seven
and eight figures online I want to talk
about automating your business what my
process is for automating our business
and how you can essentially remove
yourself from having to do all the stuff
in your business I think this is
important for people to get to so they
don't have to spend hours and hours and
hours building everything out and so
what what I use is I use a combination
of the following number one
I use
human automation okay human automation
is when I Outsource to people and you
can do this very inexpensively on a
website called
online
jobs. pH where you can actually hire
people in the Philippines to work with
you onlinejobs.ph uh I have some people
they work with me for less than $5 per
hour to be able to build out some of the
different editing videos and things like
that in our business which is awesome um
I also have some people in the United
States that manage different things
overall I have a budget where people are
doing probably about 40 hours of
different work a week that allows me to
get content out there to people and
impact people much faster so that all I
got to do is just record the content
like this send it to my team and they
get that all created they create the
landing pages they they launch the
advertisements they schedule the emails
now I still got to write the content
content I still got to record the
content and do that but I have a system
where we utilize Google Docs and Google
Docs is a platform where Google allows
you to create a document like a Word
document it's stored in the cloud and I
can just send a link to my team that way
so okay here's a Google doc for this
here's a Google doc for that here's a
doc for that and the documents have all
the information of what they need to do
of what they need to accomplish of what
their next steps are all those different
things like that okay so online jobs at
pH is great using human automation the
next thing that I use is I use AI
strategically to help me brainstorm and
I only do it when I'm actually stuck
anytime in my business that I might be
stuck I don't have an idea of maybe what
I want to do by the way that's okay like
if I'm not sure okay here's what I want
to do today to Market my business here's
how I want to say something I might have
an idea of how I want to say it but I
might need some help to figure out
exactly the right nuances and words to
say so I use Ai and I use a combination
of different AI tools one of my
favorites is
po.com which contains a number of
multiple different AI algorithms from uh
video creation to uh
Graphics stock photo images uh text
generation multiple different algorithms
on there so I use AI to help me
brainstorm different ideas now I don't
always use it like if I have an idea
what I'm always going to do first is I'm
definitely going to try to come up with
the ideas on my own without the ai's
help but sometimes I know that I have to
stay consistent in my business and I
might need to get something out there
and I don't have the time to be able to
get it done uh manually and so I use the
AI to help me with that and I'll tell
you most of the times it works really
well it works out great okay so use AI
for that and then the last thing that we
use is we use
automation tools
okay and
pre-
recorded videos okay so the combination
of this is automation tools and
pre-recorded videos is I can pre-record
content that shares with people that
coaches people that delivers value to
people this is a pre-recorded video
right here my YouTube channel is a
pre-record a video I might pre-record
certain webinars I'll pre-record my
trainings for my coaching group
um not all of them we also do have a
live class I have live interaction that
I do with people if they want me to like
to review something I will do that live
and I'll look over that we do that with
our clients in my client growth
accelerator program but anything that I
like will have a a a lot of people
watching the same piece of content and
it doesn't require a back and forth
human interaction is going to be
pre-recorded and I'm going to launch
that pre-recorded and because it's going
to save me a a lot of time I can create
the
content at any time when I want to I
have two kids under two and I'm not
making it that as an excuse It's just
has taught me like I have to automate my
business before I had kids I could make
content all day long I would spend all
day just optimizing my business and all
that and really refining everything and
making it all
perfect now I don't have time to do that
so I'm utilizing these different tools
and strategies to where I generally only
work about 5 to 10 hours a week in my
business and it helps it generates seven
figures for us okay and so this is how
automation combines I'll have some human
interaction and I'll and I'll actually
have a lot of the people that are
working with me they use AI as well so
they take my pre-recorded content filter
it into the AI through different prompts
that we've generated that way now
there's a new thing that's popping on
the scene and you might be have heard
about it called
AI
agents okay AI agents we're starting to
play around with some of these they do a
lot of the what a human automation would
do with content with AI and they
automate it with the AI itself so you
literally just filter it in and it
outputs whatever you want it to Output
automated like a computer program that
does that and so this is a whole brand
new thing that's starting to happen with
AI agents we're not using them right now
to to scale but we're using like a rough
version of it inside of when we're doing
our artificial intelligence there is no
substitute though for having a person or
a couple of different people doing
different things for you to have that
final say that final look over things
and for me anytime a message goes out in
my business anytime that it's language
that I'm
writing it's always going to be usually
it's going to be edited by me I'm
reviewing it and I'm curating it and I'm
making sure that it's exactly how I
would say it and so what I'm able to do
is I'm able to take the AI and then I'm
able to modify and adjust it that way
then I can schedule things to go out
during certain times I can schedule
social media posts I can
schedule webinar trainings I can
automate uh webinar delivery I can
automate email autoresponder delivery
the emails that go out are automated
there's a whole process where I'll
pre-write a lot of the emails and a lot
of the emails about 50 to 70% of them
are written using AI that way and and
then I'm adjusting tweaking and editing
them to make them fit exactly how I want
to say it so that's how I'm able to
remove myself from having to do a lot of
the work in my business and the AI and
and my team does most of the work for me
and then the tools that automate they
have different tasks people can show up
they can access things the pre-recorded
content so people get access to me
through pre-recorded content through
video content being able to engage that
way and that's how I'm able to deliver
the value that people come to expect all
right listen if you're a coach or mentor
and you've been trying to grow your
business growing your email list is the
number one thing that you need to do and
so that's where you want to put your
focus is you want to learn how to get
more people on your email list so that
then you can take those people build
trust with them nurture that trust and
start to close more sales and this
process right here is what I teach my
clients in my accelerator program all
the time you can check out the link
below to see our system of how we bring
in 10 to 20 brand new clients every
single month using all of this
automation all of this stuff right here
and it's not rocket science you don't
need to be a tech genius you don't need
to be need to be a techy Guru a lot of
this stuff is very easy to put together
very easy to do and that's what I show
you how to do over in that training so
go check that out Below in the
description grow your life everybody
we'll talk soon have a good one
[Applause]
[Music]